Curriculum Vitae

EXECUTIVE SECURITY 3.6+ YEARS OF EXPERIENCE IN AVIATION INDUSTRY.

Jaikishan Vinodkumar Nanwani jvnanwani22@gmail.com +91 96622 66187

SUMMARY

Vigilant and proactive Security Officer with 3.6 years + experience ensuring safe, secure, and orderly environments for Passengers and staff. Secures premises and personnel by patrolling property, monitoring surveillance equipment, and access points, permitting entry. Obtains help by sounding alarms. Prevents losses and damage by reporting irregularities; informing violators of policy and procedures; restraining trespassers.

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Looking for senior-level security officer position with reputed company to utilize superior leadership and management skills with extensive knowledge of security and safety protocols.

SKILLS

> Technical Skills:

- -> Knowledge of Surveillance & Inspection Equipments (ETD, EVD, X-Ray Screening, CCTV, DFMD, HHMD, Etc)
- -> Great Knowledge of MS Office and Basic Computer Knowledge

Professional Skills :

- -> Written and Verbal Communication
- -> Following Complex Instructions
- -> Interpersonal Skills
- -> Knowledge of Security Operations & Procedure
- -> Manage Multiple Tasks
- -> Surveillance Skills
- -> Judgment
- -> Objectivity
- -> Dependability

- -> Emotional Control
- -> Integrity
- -> Safety Management
- -> Professionalism
- -> Reporting Skills
- -> Patrolling
- -> Attention to Detail
- -> Communication
- -> Multilingual

JIME!

EXPERIENCE

- ➤ Inter Globe Aviation Indigo Airlines : 2nd Jan, 2018 to 13th Nov, 2021
 - Executive Security
 - -> search and inspect baggage & Cargo by hand as well as by operating X-ray and other equipment.
 - -> Screen passengers and airport staff prior to boarding aircraft.
 - -> Evacuate public and airport personnel in the event of an emergency.
 - -> Submit written incident reports as necessary.
 - -> Question and privately search passengers who appear to be suspicious.
 - -> Support law enforcement.
- ➤ Global Airport & Ground Services Pvt. Ltd: 15th Nov, 2021 to Present
 - Agent Security
 - -> search and inspect Cargo by hand as well as by operating X-ray and other equipment.
 - -> Evacuate public and airport personnel in the event of an emergency.
 - -> Submit written incident reports as necessary.
 - -> Support law enforcement.

EDUCATION & OTHER QUALIFICATIONS

- > SSC Sadhu Vaswani High School, GSEB, Second Class, (2010)
- > HSC Sadhu Vaswani High School, GSEB, Second Class, (2012)
- ➤ **B.com** R.C.College of Commerce , Gujarat University, Pass Class(2015)
- ➤ Diploma in Aviation, Hospitality and Tours & Travels, Frankfinn institute (2017)

ACHIEVEMENTS & CERTIFICATIONS

- ➤ Computer Certificate : Basic Computer Skills Certificate
- ➤ Basic AVSEC Certification (Cleared in First Trail) (2018 to 2020)
- ➤ Basic AVSEC Refresher (Valid till 28th Jan, 2023)
- > DGR Cat.12 (Valid till 11th Nov, 2023)
- ➤ Certification Of Screeners (Cleared in 1stTrail-Valid till 10th Feb,2023)
- > Appreciation Certificates/Awards (Fab. Debutant, Fittest of all, Etc)

A JUR

STRENGTHS

Willingness to Listen, Time Management, Communication Power, Cooperative Behavior, Will Power, Patience.

HOBBIES

Reading, Music & Surfing

PERSONAL DETAILS

Address: 84, Asharam Park, Noble Turning, Kotarpur Road Ahmedabad, Gujarat, 382475

> **Date of Birth**: 06th Feb, 1995

Gender : Male

➤ Nationality : Indian

> Marital Status : Married

➤ **Height** : 6'3"

Languages Known:

| | English | Gujarati | Hindi |
|-------|---------|----------|-------|
| Read | ✓ | | ✓ |
| Write | 1 | 1 | ✓ |
| Speak | ✓ | / | ✓ |

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that all the details furnished here are true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Jaikishan Vinodkumar Nanwani